<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Text Tools</string>
    <string name="app_desc">Collection of useful text related functions which can be accessed within many apps inside the Android System by selecting a text within it. The supported options appear in the context menu that appears after selecting a text. You may have to reveal them by pressing the 3 dots icon in the context menu. The list of supported functions will keep on growing.</string>
    <string name="app_single_op">Select the function that you would like to perform. Selected text - %1$s</string>

    <string name="features">Features</string>
    <string name="context_menu_option">Context menu option: </string>

    <string name="context_menu_whatsapp">[T\u00B2] WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="whatsapp">WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="wup_title">Text unsaved numbers in WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="wup_desc">Easily text any unsaved number in WhatsApp. Useful if you want to text people for temporary purposes.</string>

    <string name="context_menu_eval">[T\u00B2] Evaluate</string>
    <string name="eval_title">Evaluate mathematical expressions</string>
    <string name="eval_title_small">Evaluate</string>
    <string name="eval_desc">Evaluate mathematical expressions inline and replace the expression with its result. Works only on text selected that can be edited.</string>
    <string name="invalid_expression">Invalid mathematical expression</string>
    <string name="title_activity_try_out">Try It Out</string>

    <string name="try_wup">- In the below text field, type any phone number.\n- Tap and hold on the phone number you just typed.\n- Tap on the [T\u00B2] WhatsApp option. If the option is not visible, tap on the 3 dots to reveal it.\n- If the phone number is available on WhatsApp (and if WhatsApp is installed) it should open the chat in WhatsApp.</string>
    <string name="try_eval">- In the below text field, type any mathematical expression (for example, 1 + 2 + 3).\n- Tap and hold on the expression you just typed.\n- Tap on the [T\u00B2] Evaluate option. If the option is not visible, tap on the 3 dots to reveal it.\n- If the mathematical expression typed was valid, you should see its result.</string>
    <string name="try_flow_error">Unexpected error occurred</string>
    <string name="trial_success_msg">Great! You can do the same inside any app as long as you can select a text.</string>
    <string name="trial_error_msg">If it did not work, you can raise an issue in the Github repo. Would you like to do that now?</string>
    <string name="trial_success">It worked</string>
    <string name="trial_error">It did not work</string>

    <string name="app_info">App Info</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version - %1$s (%2$d)</string>

    <string name="oss_info">Open Source</string>
    <string name="oss_desc">This app is open source! Feel free to contribute, raise issue and check it out.</string>
    <string name="oss_check">Check it out</string>
    <string name="invalid_phone_number">Invalid phone number</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="prepend_country_code_title">Automatically add country code</string>
    <string name="prepend_country_code_desc">If the selected phone number does not have any country code, the preset country code will be automatically added if enabled.</string>
    <string name="messaging">Messaging</string>
    <string name="preset_country_code">Preset country code</string>
    <string name="decimal_points_title">Decimal points</string>
    <string name="decimal_points_desc">Number of digits shown after the decimal point as a result of an evaluate function. If the result is an integer (whole number with no decimal), the decimal point will not be shown.</string>
    <string name="releases">Releases page</string>

    <string name="context_menu_transform">[T\u00B2] Transform</string>
    <string name="transform">Transform</string>
    <string name="transform_message">Select how you want to transform the text</string>
    <string name="transform_long">Transform text</string>
    <string name="transform_desc">Provides various ways to transform the selected text like changing its case, wrapping it with other text and more.</string>
    <string name="wrap_text">Wrap text</string>
    <string name="change_case">Change case</string>

    <string name="wrap_message">Select the character with which you would like to wrap the text</string>
    <string name="wrap_single_inverted">\'\' (Single inverted commas)</string>
    <string name="wrap_double_inverted">\"\" (Double inverted commas)</string>
    <string name="wrap_first_bracket">() (First brackets)</string>
    <string name="wrap_curly_braces">{} (Curly braces)</string>
    <string name="wrap_square_bracket">[] (Square brackets)</string>
    <string name="custom_wrapper_text">Custom wrapper text</string>
    <string name="custom_wrapper_desc">The custom wrapper text should contain even number of letters. The first half of the custom wrapper text will be added to beginning of the selected text and the remaining will be added to the end of the selected text.</string>
    <string name="custom_wrapper_error">Custom wrapper text must contain even number of letters</string>

    <string name="change_case_message">Select how you want to change the case</string>
    <string name="upper_case">UPPER CASE</string>
    <string name="lower_case">lower case</string>
    <string name="title_case_first_word_only">Title case (first word only)</string>
    <string name="title_case_all_words">Title Case (All Words)</string>
    <string name="random_case">rAnDOm cASe</string>
    <string name="contributors">Contributors</string>

    <string name="enable_preview">Enable preview</string>
    <string name="wrap_result">Result - %1$s</string>

    <string name="editable_error">This option works only on editable text input</string>
    <string name="previewed_text_truncated">Previewed result is truncated. Transformation will be applied to the entire selection.</string>
</resources>